[

    {
        "question": "Szeretem a sajtot = I Like ______",
        "answers": [ "Cheese" ],
        "correctAnswer": "Cheese",
        "answerLanguage": "en-GB",
        "timeLimit": 30
    },
    {
        "question": "Arc = ____?",
        "answers": [ "Face" ],
        "correctAnswer": "Face",
        "answerLanguage": "en-GB",
        "timeLimit": 20
    },
    {
        "question": "Szereted a levest? = Do you like ____ ?",
        "answers": [ "Soup" ],
        "correctAnswer": "Soup",
        "answerLanguage": "en-GB",
        "timeLimit": 30
    },
    {
        "question": "Nem szeretem a joghurtot = I don't like _______!'",
        "answers": [ "Yoghurt" ],
        "correctAnswer": "Yoghurt",
        "answerLanguage": "en-GB",
        "timeLimit": 30
    },
    {
        "question": "Szőke = _____",
        "answers": [ "Blond" ],
        "correctAnswer": "Blond",
        "answerLanguage": "en-GB",
        "timeLimit": 20
    },
    {
        "question": "Sárga = ______",
        "answers": [ "Yellow" ],
        "correctAnswer": "Yellow",
        "answerLanguage": "en-GB",
        "timeLimit": 20
    },
    {
        "question": "Kék = _____",
        "answers": [ "Blue" ],
        "correctAnswer": "Blue",
        "answerLanguage": "en-GB",
        "timeLimit": 20
    },
    {
        "question": "Zöld = ______",
        "answers": [ "" ],
        "correctAnswer": "Green",
        "answerLanguage": "en-GB",
        "timeLimit": 20
    },
    {
        "question": "I see with my ____!'",
        "answers": [ "" ],
        "correctAnswer": "Eyes",
        "answerLanguage": "en-GB",
        "timeLimit": 30
    },
    {
        "question": "I hear with my ____",
        "answers": [ "" ],
        "correctAnswer": "Ears",
        "answerLanguage": "en-GB",
        "timeLimit": 30
    },
    {
        "question": "I taste with my _____",
        "answers": [ "" ],
        "correctAnswer": "Mouth",
        "AlternateAnswers": [ "Tongue" ],
        "answerLanguage": "en-GB",
        "timeLimit": 30
    },
    {
        "question": "I smell with my ____",
        "answers": [ "" ],
        "correctAnswer": "Nose",
        "answerLanguage": "en-GB",
        "timeLimit": 30
    },
    {
        "question": "I touch with my _____",
        "answers": [ "" ],
        "correctAnswer": "Hands",
        "answerLanguage": "en-GB",
        "timeLimit": 30
    },
    {
        "question": "Száj = ______",
        "answers": [ " " ],
        "correctAnswer": "Mouth",
        "answerLanguage": "en-GB",
        "timeLimit": 20
    },
    {
        "question": "Szemek = ______",
        "answers": [ " " ],
        "correctAnswer": "Eyes",
        "answerLanguage": "en-GB",
        "timeLimit": 20
    },
    {
        "question": "Szőke = ______",
        "answers": [ " " ],
        "correctAnswer": "Blond",
        "answerLanguage": "en-GB",
        "timeLimit": 20
    },
    {
        "question": "Kezek = ______",
        "answers": [ " " ],
        "correctAnswer": "Hands",
        "answerLanguage": "en-GB",
        "timeLimit": 20
    }
]